## Will

## Godwin

Web Developer

Phone: 0414 487 511

Email: willygodwin47@gmail.com

Perth, WA, Australia

LinkedIn

■ Github

% Portfolio

## PROFILE

Junior Web-Developer with a passion for creating interactive web environments.

Confident in front end and back-end development with experience in the design, installation, testing and maintenance of webapplications. Ability to acquire new skills fast and enjoy challenging myself.

Proficient in technologies such as Javascript, CSS, HTML, node.js, express.js and MySQL. Experience in C, Java and Python. Able to self-manage smaller projects or collaborate in a team environment.

## EDUCATION

#### Bachelor of Software Engineering

University of Western Australia Feb 2020 – Current

#### **Coding Bootcamp**

University of Western Australia November 2020 – May 2021

# Bachelor of Applied Science (Construction Management)

Curtin University
Feb 2015 – November 2018

## PROJECTS

## Project 1 - Reci-bits

Developed the Auto-complete feature for the search bar, used AJAX and external API's to populate the Recipe Lists and Modal Pop Up, developed the Star Button to save to favourite recipes.

#### Project 2 – Weather Dashboard

Use of AJAX and external weather API to populate current weather and 5-day forecast, search inputs and local storage to save recent searches.

### Project 3 - Coding Quiz

Array of quiz questions to be randomly chosen from for the use to answer. Use of timers and intervals. Local storage to save the top 5 highest scores or clear scoreboard.

## EXPERIENCE

#### Barista

Kirkwood Deli August 2019-Current

#### Contracts Administrator

PS Structures January 2016–January 2019

Successfully managed the subcontractor budgets for the Bethanie on the Park Aged Development and the Armadale Aquatic Aquatic Centre and worked on pricing over 50+ tenders.